# Shu Zhou

leozhoushu.lofter.com shuzhou@umich.edu +(734) 272 1958 Ann Arbor, MI Shu is a designer who is interested in user experience design, interaction prototyping and architecture design. She hopes to incorporate technology and design into our everyday life.

### **EDUCATION**

University of Michigan School of Information

Ann Arbor, MI 2016.9~2018.4

Master of Science in Information (HCI track)

GPA: 3.88/4

Tongji University
College of Architecture and Urban Planning

Shanghai, China 2011.9~2016.6 **Bachelor of Architecture** 

GPA: 4.29/5

## **PROJECTS**

Individual design of a mobile app helping detect student's emotional changes and give them instant help

Ceremony 2016.9~2016.12
Client project to develop an app for better management of participation in conference

• Openair 2016 2016.10~2016.11

Web development competition

Redesigned homepage for Summit to improve website's accessibility

Olient consulting project for Domino's Pizza
Found problems and gave recommendations for their intranet named dLive

## **EXPERIENCE**

Design Clinic (UMSI)

*Ann Arbor, MI* 2016.9~2016.12

**UX Designer | Consultant** 

- Designed wireframes and mockups for Tom Meloche
- Conducted User Research and testing with prototype
- Atelier YeAS

Shanghai, China 2016.1~2016.2

**Architectecture Intern** 

 Designed conceptual digital models, made preliminary research reports

Atelier Dehaus

Shanghai, China 2015.3~2015.6

**Architectecture Intern** 

 Draw architectural plans, used grasshopper to generate different forms

### **SKILLS**

**Design Software UX Method Programming** PS/AI/ID Interview/Brainstorm HTML5 SketchUp/Rhino Sketch/Storvboard CSS3 Persona/Scenario **AutoCAD** GitHub Wireframe Sketch/Axure Jauerv Invision/Framer.js Hi-fi Prototyping Python After Effects **Contextural Inquiry** WordPress